KOBILJON TOSHNAZAROV

1008, 100 High-Tech building Inha-ro, Nam-Gu Incheon South Korea +8210 5034 2705 kobiljon@nsl.inha.ac.kr qobiljon.github.io

SUMMARY

Expected PhD in Computer Science, expertise in the field of Human-Computer Interaction. Expert software engineer, researcher, and presenter. Most recent research and engineering experience at NSL ¹. Has collaborated with research experts from KAIST, Seoul National University, Yonsei University, INHA University, and with software engineering experts from Samsung Electronics, South Korea. Has a voluntary experience (running a club of junior programmers, mentoring in a hackathon and Touch Math festival at IUT²).

EDUCATION

- (2020–2023) PhD in Computer Science, Inha University, South Korea
- (2018–2020) MS in Computer Science, Inha University, South Korea, CGPA: 94.5 / 100
- (2014–2018) BS in Computer Science, Inha-IUT, Uzbekistan, CGPA: 84.2 / 100

PUBLICATIONS

- (2020) Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management, CHI'20 Conference Proceedings
- (2020) STDD: Short-Term Depression Detection with Passive Sensing, MDPI Sensors Journal
- (2020) IMSP an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection, KICS'20 Conference Proceedings
- (2019) EasyTrack: Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies, MobiSys'19 Conference Proceedings

EXPERIENCE

- (2019–Present) Research Assistant at NSL
 - Suicidality prevention with wearables (passive sensing, digital phenotyping)
 - Stress, depression detection with wearables and smartphones (passive sensing)
 - Digital therapeutics / interventions
 - Abnormal behavior tracking
- (2018–2019) Lecture Assistant at Inha University
 - Application Programming in Java courses
 - Computer Networks courses (link: rb.gy/higlst)

SKILLS

- C++ (11, 14, 17), Java (7, 8), Kotlin, Python, C#, SQL
- OOP concepts, Algorithms and Data Structures
- Interpersonal skills, Public speaking, Conceptual thinking, Critical thinking and Analysis, Research

LANGUAGES

- English full professional user (IELTS speaking 8.5 / 9)
- Russian & Uzbek native bilingual user

¹ Networking System's Lab – nsl.inha.ac.kr (Incheon, South Korea)

² Inha University in Tashkent – inha.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)